braveheartwomen.com 2011-05-25

# Braveheart Women Privacy Policy: BraveHeart Women

**PRIVACY POLCIY**

**BRAVEHEART WOMEN GLOBAL COMMUNITY**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 15, 2009

At BraveHeart Women Global Community, we are committed to maintaining your privacy and your trust. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, protect, use and share information about you when you use the BraveHeart Women Global Community website (the "Site"). We hope this information increases your confidence in BraveHeart Women Global Community and enhances your experience on our Site. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the BraveHeart Women Global Community Terms of Use Agreement. Each time that you use the Site, you signify that you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using the Service and terminate your membership.

**PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE FOR BRAVEHEART WOMEN GLOBAL COMMUNITY CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO SUCH PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE.**

**Information We Collect**

When you register with BraveHeart Women Global Community you provide us with certain personal information such as your name, your email address, and select a user name and password. Once you are registered, you may be given the option to add additional personal information about yourself, your interests, personal and business. Other than the basic information required for registration you should add information which you wish other members to see.

We may also collect information regarding your interaction with other users and your use of the Site. From time to time we may ask you to respond to surveys or other requests for information and we collect the information you provide. We collect this information so that we can provide you quality services and offer features which will benefit all members of the community

You post User Content (as defined in the [Terms of Use](http://www.braveheartwomen.com/customhtml.jspa?page=terms)) on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on the site is a violation of the BraveHeart Women Terms of Use and should be reported to [info@braveheartwomen.com](http://www.braveheartwomen.com/Local%20Settings/Temporary%20Internet%20Files/Local%20Settings/Temporary%20Internet%20Files/OLK187/info@braveheartwomen.com)

We may also collect information regarding your interaction with other users and your use of the Site. From time to time we may ask you to respond to surveys or other requests for information and we collect the information you provide. We may also collect information about you through other methods, including research surveys or information we obtain from third parties, including verification services, data services, as well as public sources. We use this information to continually offer you the most value as a BraveHeart Women Global Community Member.

Like many standard Website servers, we collect information from all visitors to the Site. This information may include the browser you are using, the internet address from which you linked to our Site, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer you used to access our Site, and usage and browsing habits. We use this information to help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, to analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.

To help make sure you receive information that is relevant to you, our Site uses data "cookies." These cookies are small data files stored on your computer which identify you as a previous visitor to the Site and help us to personalize your experience when you arrive. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. You can instruct your browser not to accept cookies. However, if you disable this function, you will not be able to use some of the features on our Site.

Our Web pages and our e-mail newsletters contain "web beacons." Web beacons allow us to count users that have visited a web page or opened an email that contains a web beacon and collect other types of aggregate information. Using this information, we are able to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Site. This allows us to learn what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which parts of our Site are the most interesting and what kind of offers our Members like to see. Some of the web beacons that are in place on our Site are used only by BraveHeart Women Global Community, and other web beacons are from our vendors and advertisers who use this data to assist us in analyzing how our Members use the Site. In addition, we have agreements with various affiliate networks that promote BraveHeart Women Global Community on their affiliate websites. These affiliate advertisers may use web beacons in their advertisements to track users who click through from the affiliate website to the Site.

**Individuals Under Age 18**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for BraveHeart Women Global Community or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us at _[info@braveheartwomen.com](mailto:info@braveheartwomen.com)._

**How We Use Your Information**

BraveHeart Women Global Community uses the information you provide for several purposes, such as to communicate with you and to give you a better experience when visiting the site by personalizing tools, content, services and email messages. We also use this information to build new services and develop offers that we believe are more relevant and valuable to you. 

The information collected by us is also used to create aggregated portraits of the BraveHeart Women Global Community audience, portraits which present anonymous statistical demographic information but no personally identifiable information. This aggregated information is used, among other things, to determine trends and needs, and also to supply market research to potential advertisers and partners to help them understand who our audience is.

Information you submit to us will be available to users of BraveHeart Women Global Community who belong to at least one of the communities which you also belong to who you allow to access the information through your privacy community. Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the BraveHeart Women Global Community site and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so other members can find you. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (member of your personal community) that allows such access based on your privacy settings.

We may send you service-related announcements and emails from time to time.

On occasion, we are able to offer you special products or services through a relationship with a third party. In those cases, the offer will be brought to you by BraveHeart Women Global Community and fulfilled by the third party. If you accept the offer, you will become a customer of the company that is fulfilling the offer and we will not have control over their use of the personally identifiable information that you provide to them when you accept the offer.

We may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a brand or movie and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you this service. We believe this benefits you. 

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the BraveHeart Women Global Community service or using the BraveHeart Women Global Community name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

In the event that BraveHeart Women Global Community, substantially all of its assets, or a line of business are acquired or merged with another company, personally identifiable information of our Members may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. BraveHeart Women Global Community will notify users of the Site of such a change in ownership or transfer of assets by posting a notice on the Site.

**Links**

BraveHeart Women Global Community may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by BraveHeart Women Global Community.

**Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on the site are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. BraveHeart Women Global Community does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on BraveHeart Women Global Community unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by BraveHeart Women Global Community and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**Updating Your Personal Information**

If you are a BraveHeart Women Global Community Member, you can update your personally identifiable information at any time. To do this, just click on the "Edit Profile" link listed throughout the Site. However, we are unable to update or delete any of your personally identifiable information that has been shared with a third party as permitted in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Policy. We will inform you if we substantially modify the way we handle your personally identifiable information by posting a notice on the Site, and we will give you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy you can contact us at [info@braveheartwomen.com](mailto:info@braveheartwomen.com). 

You can also write us at:

BraveHeart Women Global Community

1426 Towne Lake Parkway, Suite 102-277

Woodstock, Georgia 30189
